<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>GBergatto</title><link>http://gbergatto.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on GBergatto</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.139.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:14:49 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://gbergatto.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exploring Tools For Managing Your Dotfiles</title><link>http://gbergatto.github.io/posts/tools-managing-dotfiles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:14:49 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://gbergatto.github.io/posts/tools-managing-dotfiles/</guid><description>&lt;p>It’s been almost 2 years since I installed Arch on my laptop, and I feel like
my dotfiles are becoming more and more disorganized. I still have configuration
files from programs I no longer use, and keeping track of how I customize the
ones I do use is taking far more effort than it should. To address this, I’ve
decided to put my dotfiles under version control, so I can have a clearer view
of how they change over time.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Installing Flutter and Android SKD on Arch Linux without Android Studio</title><link>http://gbergatto.github.io/posts/flutter-installation-arch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 18:33:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://gbergatto.github.io/posts/flutter-installation-arch/</guid><description>&lt;p>Having recently switched from Arcolinux to Arch Linux, I needed to reinstall Flutter on my laptop. The last time I did this, I installed Android Studio because it seemed like the easiest way to get the Android SDK working. However, I never used it as an IDE, so it was hard to justify keeping it on my system since it takes up more than 30GB.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This time, with a year of Linux experience under my belt, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to install and configure everything needed to build apps for Android without having to install Android Studio. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how I did it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chronicles Of My First Arch Installation</title><link>http://gbergatto.github.io/posts/chronicles-arch-installation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 12:11:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://gbergatto.github.io/posts/chronicles-arch-installation/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to start a blog for a couple of months now, but I kept putting it off it, not knowing what to write about at first. Last week I installed Arch Linux on my laptop, so I guess this is the right place to start.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what Arch Linux is, I&amp;rsquo;m glad to be the one to introduce it to you. You can read more about it &lt;a href="https://archlinux.org/about/">here&lt;/a>. You may also want to get more familiar with Linux in general before reading the rest of this blog post.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>http://gbergatto.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://gbergatto.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>A page to explain who I am and what this blog is about.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>